[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "Take a break from the lessons and have a short quiz. But first, let’s review what you’ve learned.",
    "prompt": "You’ve learned about the small vowels and how they’re used to create sounds missing in the native Japanese sound set. Let's review:",
    "options": [
      "Ti – ティ",
      "Tu – トゥ",
      "She – シェ",
      "Je – ジェ",
      "Di – ディ",
      "Du – ドゥ",
      "Che – チェ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "F and W",
    "options": [
      "Fa – ファ",
      "Fi – フィ",
      "Fu – フ",
      "Fe – フェ",
      "Fo – フォ",
      "Wa – ワ",
      "Wi – ウィ",
      "Wu/U – ウ",
      "We – ウェ",
      "Wo – ウォ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "V",
    "options": ["Va – ヴァ", "Vi – ヴィ", "Vu – ヴ", "Ve – ヴェ", "Vo – ヴォ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "You’ve also learned about long vowels (ー) and the small “ッ”",
    "options": ["Kohi – コーヒー", "Keki – ケーキ", "Poketto – ポケット", "Baggu – バッグ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "She",
    "options": ["シェ", "シゥ", "シォ", "シャ"],
    "answer": "シェ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Che",
    "options": ["チョ", "チャ", "チェ", "チュ"],
    "answer": "チェ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Du",
    "options": ["ドィ", "ドァ", "ドゥ", "ドェ"],
    "answer": "ドゥ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ti",
    "options": ["テォ", "ティ", "テァ", "テゥ"],
    "answer": "ティ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Va",
    "options": ["ヴォ", "ヴィ", "ヴェ", "ヴァ"],
    "answer": "ヴァ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Vu",
    "options": ["ヴ", "バ", "ダ", "ゴ"],
    "answer": "ヴ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Fo",
    "options": ["ファ", "フェ", "フォ", "フィ"],
    "answer": "フォ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Fa",
    "options": ["フォ", "ファ", "フィ", "フェ"],
    "answer": "ファ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Wo",
    "options": ["ヲ", "ウォ", "ウェ", "ウィ"],
    "answer": "ウォ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Wi",
    "options": ["ウェ", "ウォ", "ウィ", "ウァ"],
    "answer": "ウィ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Keki",
    "options": ["ケーキー", "カーキ", "ケーキ", "コーヒー"],
    "answer": "ケーキ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Baggu",
    "options": ["バッグ", "ポケット", "バッド", "タップ"],
    "answer": "バッグ"
  }
]